

ENGLISH: B1

LOCATION: Ourense, Spain LINKEDIN: danielcambalamas MAIL: cambalamas@gmail.com PORTFOLIO: www.cambalamas.com

SKILLS

Object Oriented Programming

3D Maths & Physics

Python

• • • • •

OpenGL & GLSL

Go (GoLang)

Unity

SQL & NoSQL

MVC & SOLID

Docker

• • • • •

Linux & Bash

• • 0 0

Multithreading

Javascript (Vanilla)

• 0 0

Networking (TCP/IP)

• • 0 0 0

Git

HTML & CSS

• • • • •

PROJECTS

Obtaining an interactive 3D skeleton from motion capture files, interpolating between animations to generate the transitions.



Cat & Mouse recreation with decision tree based AI system with safe areas, targets and power-ups.

Static states designer

C

Component-based states of any false-prototype.

ABOUT ME

In my roadmap to be a great computer graphics engineer. I moved from Galicia to Madrid after get my BSc in Computer Science, for get a MSc in Computer Graphics. Parallely, waking me up at 5 in the morning to still study about low-level graphics APIs and game development, I worked as researcher in an EIT-Health project as backend & graphic engineer in a Unity3D tool for M.I.S surgery training.

I'm cooperative, passionate, committed and fastlearner and confident in agile development.

EXPERIENCE

BackEnd & Graphics Sottware Engineer

GBT UPM 06/2018 - 06/2019

Referral Letter

- Reduction of 75% the code to maintain, implementing a RESTful API for the DB's C.R.U.D. moving so from a monolithic architecture to services one.
- Improve the surgeons' UX during the evaluation of its students designing a web app to digest metrics from the project main tool.
- Construction of the brand of the project from the logos to the landing page, achieving a strong visual identity adapted to the target market.

Backend Software Engineer

Profocus 01/2017 - 04/2017

Automation of internal processes in the production line of a e-commerce photography studio, from product reception to the invoicing stage. Centralizing each order and saving time and resources.

EDUCATION

MSc in Computer Graphics, Games and Virtual Reality

U. Rey Juan Carlos 2017 - 2019

BSc in Computer Science

U. of Vigo (ESEI) 2012 - 2017